Guide to the Gregory Breit Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1932-1973; Series I; 14.5 linear feet (29 boxes)
  - Kyoto University, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 521, Reel 7U)
    Department of Industrial Chemistry
  - Kyoto University, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 522, Reel 7U)
  - Ladenburg, R., 1934, undated (Box 13, Folder 523, Reel 8U)
  - Lamb, Willis E., Jr., 1937-1938, 1947-1948, 1950, 1965-1966, undated (Box 13, Folder 524, Reel 8U)
  - Lane, Anthony M., 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 525, Reel 8U)
  - Langley, Doris C., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 526, Reel 8U)
  - Lapidus, L. I., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 527, Reel 8U)
  - Laporte, Otto, 1954, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 528, Reel 8U)
  - Lasher, Gordon, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 529, Reel 8U)
  - Lassila, Kenneth E., 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 530, Reel 8U)
  - Lauritsen, Charles C., 1937, 1948, 1951, 1965, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 531, Reel 8U)
  - Lauritsen, Thomas, 1947-1949, 1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 532, Reel 8U)
  - Lawrence, Ernest O., [1934], 1946, 1948-1953 (Box 13, Folder 533, Reel 8U)
  - Lawrence Radiation Laboratory, 1950-1954, 1957-1958, 1962-1964, 1966-1970, undated (Box 13, Folder 534-536, Reel 8U)
  - Lebedev Institute, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 537, Reel 8U)
  - Lederman, Leon, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 538, Reel 8U)
  - Lee, P. H. C., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 539, Reel 8U)
  - Lee, Tsung-Dao, 1957, 1962, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 540, Reel 8U)
  - Lehar, F., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 541, Reel 8U)
  - Lehman, Charles A., 1953, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 542, Reel 8U)
  - Lehmann, H., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 543, Reel 8U)
  - Levinger, Joseph S., 1956-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 544, Reel 8U)
  - Levintov, I. I., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 545, Reel 8U)
  - Lévy, Maurice, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 546, Reel 8U)
  - Lewis, Charles, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 547, Reel 8U)
  - Lewis, James P., 1966, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 548, Reel 8U)
  - Lewis, R. R., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 549, Reel 8U)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 550, Reel 8U)
  - Libby, W. F., 1951, 1954, 1957, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 551, Reel 8U)
  - Library of Congress, 1954, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 552, Reel 8U)
  - Liebowitz, Benjamin, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 553, Reel 8U)
  - Lin, Duo-Liang, 1961-1967 (Box 14, Folder 554, Reel 8U)
  - Lin, Frank C., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 555, Reel 8U)
  - Linford, Leon B., 1956 (Box 14, Folder 556, Reel 8U)
  - Ling, Daniel S., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 557, Reel 8U)
  - Lipkin, Harry J., 1960 (Box 14, Folder 558, Reel 8U)
  - Lipski, Alfons, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 559, Reel 8U)
  - Livingston, M. Stanley, 1954, 1956, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 560, Reel 8U)
  - Livingston, Robert S., 1951-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 561, Reel 8U)
  - Lodhi, M. A. K., 1969-1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 562, Reel 8U)
  - Lomon, Earle, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 563, Reel 8U)
  - Loomis, F. W., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 564, Reel 8U)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory, 1948, 1950-1951, 1953-1955, 1958-1959, 1961-1964, 1967-1968, 1971-1972, undated (Box 14, Folder 565-568, Reel 8U)
  - Lott, Elizabeth, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 569, Reel 8U)
  - Loucks, Vernon R., undated (Box 14, Folder 570, Reel 8U)
  - Loughridge, Donald H., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 571, Reel 8U)
  - Louisiana State University, 1951, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 572, Reel 8U)
  - Lovelace, C., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 573, Reel 8U)
  - Lowan, Arnold N., 1947-1950, undated (Box 14, Folder 574-575, Reel 8U)
  - Lowen, Irving S., 1936, 1940, 1946-1949, undated (Box 14, Folder 576, Reel 8U)
  - Lowry, Edward D., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 577, Reel 8U)
  - Lu, An-Hua, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 578, Reel 8U)
  - Lucas, Jerome G., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 579, Reel 8U)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 580, Reel 8U)
  - Luke, Perry J., 1951-1956 (Box 14, Folder 581, Reel 8U)
  - Lynton, Ernest A., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 582, Reel 8U)
  - McCarthy, Ian, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 583, Reel 8U)
  - McCarthy, Richard D., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 584, Reel 8U)
  - McDonald, F. Alan, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 585, Reel 8U)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 586, Reel 9U)
  - McGowan, F. K., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 587, Reel 9U)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1939, 1947, 1955, 1958-1961, 1964-1968, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 588-590, Reel 9U)
  - MacGregor, Malcolm H., 1964-1965, 1967, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 591, Reel 9U)
  - McHale, John L., Jr., 1950, 1954-1957, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 592, Reel 9U)
  - Machlup, Stefan, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 593, Reel 9U)
  - McIntosh, E. C., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 594, Reel 9U)
  - McIntosh, John S., 1949-1950, 1952-1953, 1955-1956, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 595, Reel 9U)
  - McIntyre, John A., 1956-1957, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 596, Reel 9U)
  - McIntyre, John A., 1963-1967, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 597, Reel 9U)
  - Mack, Julian E., 1951-1954, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 598, Reel 9U)
  - McKee, Jasper S. C., 1971-1972, undated (Box 15, Folder 599, Reel 9U)
  - McKeehan, L. W., 1951, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 600, Reel 9U)
  - McKibben, J. L., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 601, Reel 9U)
  - Macklin, R. L., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 602, Reel 9U)
  - MacLachlan, James, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 603, Reel 9U)
  - McMaster University, 1955, 1963, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 604, Reel 9U)
  - McMillan, Edwin M., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 605, Reel 9U)
  - Macmillan Company, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 606, Reel 9U)
  - McNally, J. Rand, Jr., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 607, Reel 9U)
  - McNeill, K. G., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 608, Reel 9U)
  - Maglíc, B., 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 609, Reel 9U)
  - Malik, Fazley Bary, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 610, Reel 9U)
  - Malli, Guljari L., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 611, Reel 9U)
  - Mandl, F., 1960 (Box 15, Folder 612, Reel 9U)
  - Manley, John H., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 613, Reel 9U)
  - Mann, A. K., 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 614, Reel 9U)
  - Mann, W. B., 1944, 1968, undated (Box 15, Folder 615, Reel 9U)
  - Manning, L. A., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 616, Reel 9U)
  - Mano, Koichi, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 617, Reel 9U)
  - Manufacturers and Traders Trust Company, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 618, Reel 9U)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1951, 1953-1959, 1961-1962, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 619, Reel 9U)
  - Maria Sklodowska-Curie Centenary Committee, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 620, Reel 9U)
  - Marion, Jerry, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 621, Reel 9U)
  - Mark, Carson, 1951, 1953-1955 (Box 15, Folder 622, Reel 9U)
  - Mark, Hans, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 623, Reel 9U)
  - Mark Twain Journal, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 624, Reel 9U)
  - Marshak, Robert E., 1946-1950, 1953-1955, 1957-1960, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 625, Reel 9U)
  - Marshall, Leona, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 626, Reel 9U)
  - Marshall, Thomas, Jr., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 627, Reel 9U)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1944, 1951, 1958, 1966-1967, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 628, Reel 9U)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Press, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 629, Reel 9U)
  - Masso, Joseph F., 1961, 1965, 1967-1968, undated (Box 16, Folder 630, Reel 9U)
  - Masterson, Kleber S., Jr., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 631, Reel 9U)
  - Mathematical Computing Service, 1950-1951 (Box 16, Folder 632, Reel 9U)
  - Mathematical Reviews, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 633, Reel 9U)
  - Mathematical Tables Project, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 634, Reel 9U)
  - Max-Planck-Institut Für Physik, 1958, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 635, Reel 9U)
  - Mayer, Harris, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 636, Reel 9U)
  - Mayer, Maria Goeppert, 1952, 1958, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 637, Reel 9U)
  - Meeting on Nucleon-Nucleon and Pion-Nucleon Interactions, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 638, Reel 9U)
  - Melkanoff, M. A., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 639, Reel 9U)
  - Menzel, Donald H., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 640, Reel 9U)
  - Merriam, John C., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 641, Reel 9U)
  - Meyerott, Roland E., 1949-1953, 1955, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 642, Reel 9U)
  - Michels, Walter C., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 643, Reel 9U)
  - Miner, Harlan S., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 644, Reel 9U)
  - Mirand, Edwin A., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 645, Reel 9U)
  - Mitchell, Allan C. G., 1934-1941, 1945-1946, 1948-1950, 1953-1956, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 646-648, Reel 9U)
  - Mitchell, Maurice B., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 649, Reel 9U)
  - Mohler, Fred L., 1946 (Box 16, Folder 650, Reel 9U)
  - Mohr, C. B. O., 1934 (Box 16, Folder 651, Reel 9U)
  - Monroe Calculating Machine Company, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 652, Reel 9U)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 653, Reel 9U)
  - Moore, Samuel A., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 654, Reel 9U)
  - Moravcsik, Michael J., 1958-1960, 1962-1964, 1966-1967, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 655-656, Reel 9U)
  - Morse, Philip M., 1947-1948, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 657, Reel 9U)
  - Moshinsky, Marcus, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 658, Reel 9U)
  - Moszkowski, Steven A., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 659, Reel 9U)
  - Mottelson, Benjamin R., 1957-1958, 1964, undated (Box 16, Folder 660, Reel 9U)
  - Mott-Smith, Harold, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 661, Reel 9U)
  - Motz, Henry T., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 662, Reel 9U)
  - Mukherjee, Shankar N., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 663, Reel 9U)
  - Mulliken, Robert S., 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 664, Reel 9U)
  - Murnaghan, Francis D., 1939, 1948, 1951, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 665-666, Reel 9U)
  - Murphy, Edgar J., 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 667, Reel 9U)
  - Murray, F. H., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 668, Reel 9U)
  - Musher, J. I., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 669, Reel 9U)
  - Muslim University, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 670, Reel 9U)
  - Myers, Frank E., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 671, Reel 9U)
  - Nagamiya, Shoji, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 672, Reel 9U)
  - Napolitano, E., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 673, Reel 9U)
  - Nath, Pran, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 674, Reel 9U)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.), 1940, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 675, Reel 9U)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.), 1958-1963, 1965-1966, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 676-677, Reel 10U)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.), 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 678, Reel 10U)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.), 1950-1951, 1954-1961, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 679-681, Reel 10U)
    Editorial Board
  - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 682, Reel 10U)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1966-1967, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 683, Reel 10U)
  - National Military Establishment (U.S.), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 684, Reel 10U)
  - National Physical Laboratory New Delhi, India, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 685, Reel 10U)
  - National Research Council (U.S.), 1932, 1934, 1938, 1945-1946, 1950-1958, 1961, 1964, 1966, 1968, 1971, undated (Box 17, Folder 686-689, Reel 10U)
  - National Science Foundation, 1952-1969, 1970 (Feb)-1970 (Apr), 1970 (Jun)-1970 (Dec) (Box 17, Folder 690-698, Reel 10U)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971-1972, undated (Box 18, Folder 699, Reel 10U)
  - National Science Fund, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 700, Reel 10U)
  - National Teacher Placement Service, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 701, Reel 10U)
  - Naval Ordnance Laboratory, 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 702, Reel 10U)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1947, 1950-1951, 1957, 1959-1960, 1969, 1971-1972, undated (Box 18, Folder 703, Reel 10U)
  - New York University, 1934, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 704, Reel 10U)
  - Newton, John O., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 705, Reel 10U)
  - Newton, Roger G., 1957, 1960, undated (Box 18, Folder 706, Reel 10U)
  - Niels Bohr Institutet, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 707, Reel 10U)
  - Nierenberg, William O., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 708, Reel 10U)
  - Nishida, Yoshihiko, 1958-1967, 1971-1972, undated (Box 18, Folder 709-710, Reel 10U)
  - Noerdlinger, Peter D., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 711, Reel 10U)
  - Nogami, Yukihisa, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 712, Reel 10U)
  - Northcliffe, L. C., 1955-1957 (Box 18, Folder 713, Reel 10U)
  - North-Holland Publishing Company, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 714, Reel 10U)
  - Nova University, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 715, Reel 10U)
  - Novick, Robert, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 716, Reel 10U)
  - Noyes, H. Pierre, 1960-1970 (Box 18, Folder 717-719, Reel 10U)
  - Nucleon-Nucleon Interaction Conference, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 720, Reel 10U)
  - Nucleonics, 1947, 1955, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 721, Reel 10U)
  - Nunemaker, Rodney, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 722, Reel 10U)
  - Nuovo Cimento, Il, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 723, Reel 10U)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1948, 1950-1962, 1965, 1968, 1972, undated (Box 18, Folder 724, Reel 11U)
  - O'Connell, Robert F., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 725, Reel 11U)
  - O'Dwyer, Terry F., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 726, Reel 11U)
  - Ohio State University, 1957, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 727, Reel 11U)
  - Ohnuma, Shoroku, 1953-1955, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 728, Reel 11U)
  - Okamoto, K., 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 729, Reel 11U)
  - Onsager, Lars, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 730, Reel 11U)
  - Oppenheimer, John F., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 731, Reel 11U)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1934-1936, 1938-1939, 1942-1943, 1945, 1947, 1951-1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1960, 1963, undated (Box 19, Folder 732, Reel 11U)
  - Optical Society of America, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 733, Reel 11U)
  - Oregon State University, 1953, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 734, Reel 11U)
  - Ould, Richard Sheldon, 1955, 1957, 1962-1964, 1967, undated (Box 19, Folder 735, Reel 11U)
  - Oxley, Charles L., 1952 (Box 19, Folder 736, Reel 11U)
  - Pais, A., 1946-1947, 1950, 1967, undated (Box 19, Folder 737, Reel 11U)
  - Pal, Manoj Kumar, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 738, Reel 11U)
  - Palevsky, Harry, 1962-1963, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 739, Reel 11U)
  - Palmieri, Joseph N., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 740, Reel 11U)
  - Pan American World Airways System, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 741, Reel 11U)
  - Panex, Inc., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 742, Reel 11U)
  - Panjab University, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 743, Reel 11U)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang K. H., 1956, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 744, Reel 11U)
  - Park, Shim C., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 745, Reel 11U)
  - Parker, Hermon, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 746, Reel 11U)
  - Particle Interactions at High Energy (conference), 1969 (Box 19, Folder 747, Reel 11U)
  - Pauli, Wolfgang, 1937, 1940, 1951, 1955-1956, undated (Box 19, Folder 748, Reel 11U)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1953, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 749, Reel 11U)
  - Pearse, Cabell A., 1956, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 750, Reel 11U)
  - Peierls, R. E., 1952-1954, 1959, 1964, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 751, Reel 11U)
  - Pergamon Press, 1953, 1957-1960, undated (Box 19, Folder 752, Reel 11U)
  - Perkins, J. L., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 753, Reel 11U)
  - Perlmutter, Arnold, undated (Box 19, Folder 754, Reel 11U)
  - Perring, John K., 1963, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 755, Reel 11U)
  - Phillips, Gerald C., 1966-1968, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 756, Reel 11U)
  - Phillips, R. J. N., 1956, 1958-1959, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 757, Reel 11U)
  - Physical Review, 1937, 1939, 1942, 1947, 1961-1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 758-761, Reel 11U)
  - Physical Review Letters, 1958, 1960-1963, 1965, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 762, Reel 11U)
  - Physical Science, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 763, Reel 11U)
  - Physics Today, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 764, Reel 11U)
  - Pieper, George F., 1957, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 765, Reel 11U)
  - Piore, Emanuel R., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 766, Reel 11U)
  - Pitman Publishing Corporation, 1946-1948, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 767, Reel 11U)
  - Pitzer, K. S., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 768, Reel 11U)
  - Plenum Press, Inc., 1964, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 769, Reel 11U)
  - Pocono Conference on Theoretical Physics, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 770, Reel 11U)
  - Poggendorff-Redaktion, 1964, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 771, Reel 11U)
  - Polak, Joel A., 1964-1966, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 772, Reel 11U)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1950, 1958, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 773, Reel 11U)
  - Porter, William S., 1957-1959, 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 774, Reel 11U)
  - Postma, Hans, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 775, Reel 11U)
  - Powell, John L., 1951, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 776, Reel 11U)
  - Prakash, Arnand, 1966, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 777, Reel 11U)
  - Prentice Hall, Inc., 1963 (Box 20, Folder 778, Reel 11U)
  - President's Committee on the National Medal of Science, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 779, Reel 11U)
  - Preston, M. A., 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 780, Reel 11U)
  - Price, Derek J. de Solla, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 781, Reel 11U)
  - Princeton University, 1946, 1949-1950, 1954-1955, 1959, 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 782, Reel 11U)
  - Princeton University Press, 1947, 1963-1965, undated (Box 20, Folder 783, Reel 11U)
  - Professional Quarterly Review, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 784, Reel 11U)
  - Progress of Theoretical Physics, 1950, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 785, Reel 11U)
  - Purtell, William A., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 786, Reel 11U)
  - Pyatt, K. D., Jr., 1967 (Box 20, Folder 787, Reel 11U)
  - Rabi, I. I. (Box 20, Folder 788, Reel 11U)
  - Rabi, I. I. (Box 20, Folder 789, Reel 11U)
  - Radio Corporation of America, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 790, Reel 11U)
  - Ramsey, Norman F., 1956-1958, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 791, Reel 11U)
  - The Rand Corporation, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 792, Reel 11U)
  - Rarita, William, 1938, 1954, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 793, Reel 11U)
  - Ratcliffe, Jack A., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 794, Reel 11U)
  - Rawitscher, George, 1958-1960, 1962-1968 (Box 20, Folder 795, Reel 11U)
  - Rawson, Edward B., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 796, Reel 11U)
  - Raysor, Ortman, Barbour, Welch and Bell, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 797, Reel 11U)
  - Recent Progress in Nuclear Physics with Tandems (conference), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 798, Reel 11U)
  - Reed, Harold, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 799, Reel 11U)
  - Reid, Roderick V., Jr., 1965, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 800, Reel 11U)
  - Reines, Frederick, 1961, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 801, Reel 11U)
  - Republican National Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 802, Reel 11U)
  - Research Corporation, 1947, 1954, 1956, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 803, Reel 11U)
  - Research Institute for Fundamental Physics, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 804, Reel 11U)
  - Revelle, Roger R., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 805, Reel 11U)
  - Reviews of Modern Physics, 1951, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 806, Reel 11U)
  - Reviews of Modern Physics, 1955, 1959, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 807, Reel 12U)
  - Reynolds, H. L., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 808)
  - Reynolds, Joseph M., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 809, Reel 12U)
  - Rice University, 1962, 1965-1967, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 810, Reel 12U)
  - Richards, Hugh T., 1947, 1950, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 811, Reel 12U)
  - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Company, Inc., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 812, Reel 12U)
  - Richtmyer, Robert D., 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 813, Reel 12U)
  - Rickover, H. G., 1946 (Box 20, Folder 814, Reel 12U)
  - Rigden, John S., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 815, Reel 12U)
  - Roberts, Arthur, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 816, Reel 12U)
  - Roberts, Juanita D., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 817, Reel 12U)
  - Roberts, Richard B., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 818, Reel 12U)
  - Robinson, Dennis M., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 819, Reel 12U)
  - Robl, Hermann, 1955-1956, 1958, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 820, Reel 12U)
  - Rockefeller Institute, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 821, Reel 12U)
  - Rohrlich, Fritz, 1959-1960, 1962, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 822, Reel 12U)
  - Rojansky, V., 1948, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 823, Reel 12U)
  - Rollefson, R., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 824, Reel 12U)
  - Roman, Paul, 1967, 1971-1972, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 825, Reel 12U)
  - Rose, Basil, 1955, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 826, Reel 12U)
  - Rose, M. E., 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 827, Reel 12U)
  - Rosen, Louis, 1958, 1963-1965, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 828, Reel 12U)
  - Rosenberg, Harvey J., 1967 (Box 20, Folder 829, Reel 12U)
  - Rosenfeld, L., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 830, Reel 12U)
  - Roth, Benjamin, 1951-1952, 1955, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 831, Reel 12U)
  - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 832, Reel 12U)
  - Ruark, Arthur E., 1934-1935, 1937-1938, 1940-1941, 1944, 1946-1950, 1952-1953, 1957, 1959-1960, 1968-1969, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 833, Reel 12U)
  - Rumbaugh, L. H., 1937 (Box 20, Folder 834, Reel 12U)
  - Runge, Richard, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 835, Reel 12U)
  - Ruppel, Hans M., 1958-1959, 1961-1965, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 836, Reel 12U)
  - Rusk, Dean, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 837, Reel 12U)
  - Russell, James E., 1957-1958, 1960, 1963-1965, undated (Box 21, Folder 838, Reel 12U)
  - Rustgi, Moti L., 1957-1963, 1966-1968, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 839-841, Reel 12U)
  - Ryu, Norio, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 842, Reel 12U)
  - Sachs, Robert G., 1947, 1949-1950, 1952-1955, 1958, 1960, 1964, 1967-1968, 1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 843, Reel 12U)
  - Sack, Seymour, 1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 844, Reel 12U)
  - Sadlak, Antoni N., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 845, Reel 12U)
  - Saha Institute of Nuclear Physics, 1960, undated (Box 21, Folder 846, Reel 12U)
  - Sailor, Vance L., 1952-1953, 1955, 1957, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 847, Reel 12U)
  - Sakurai, J. J., 1960 (Box 21, Folder 848, Reel 12U)
  - Salant, E. O., 1957, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 849, Reel 12U)
  - Salpeter, E. E., 1952, 1957-1958, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 850, Reel 12U)
  - Salyanavayana, Rao V., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 851, Reel 12U)
  - Sandia Corporation, 1948, 1951, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 852, Reel 12U)
  - Sankaranarayanan, A., 1964 (Box 21, Folder 853, Reel 12U)
  - Saperstein, Alvin M., 1955, 1957-1959, 1961, 1967, 1969, undated (Box 21, Folder 854, Reel 12U)
  - Schaal, Eric, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 855, Reel 12U)
  - Schaerf, Carlo, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 856, Reel 12U)
  - Schiff, Leonard I., 1964-1967, undated (Box 22, Folder 857, Reel 12U)
  - Schlundt, Herman, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 858, Reel 12U)
  - Schmidt, E. H., 1953 (Box 22, Folder 859, Reel 12U)
  - Schrils, Rudolph, 1962-1964, 1968, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 860, Reel 12U)
  - Schrödinger, Erwin, 1956, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 861, Reel 12U)
  - Schultz, Howard L., 1966, 1967, 1969-1972, undated (Box 22, Folder 862, Reel 12U)
  - Schwinger, Julian, 1948, 1950-1951, 1955, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 863, Reel 12U)
  - Science, 1952-1953, 1963-1966, 1970-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 864, Reel 12U)
  - Science Service, 1937, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 865, Reel 12U)
  - Scientific and Technical Information Facility, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 866, Reel 12U)
  - Scientific Research, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 867, Reel 12U)
  - Scuola di Studi Superiori Sugli Idrocarburi, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 868, Reel 12U)
  - Seaborg, Glenn T., 1948, 1959, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 869, Reel 12U)
  - Seamon, Robert E., 1965-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 870-871, Reel 12U)
  - Second National Bank of New Haven, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 872, Reel 12U)
  - Segrè, Emilio, 1945, 1949, 1952, 1954, 1956, 1959, 1963, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 873, Reel 12U)
  - Sellschop, J. P. F., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 874, Reel 12U)
  - Seven Bookhunters, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 875, Reel 12U)
  - Shacklett, Robert L., 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 876, Reel 12U)
  - Shankland, R. S., 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 877, Reel 12U)
  - Shapiro, Maurice M., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 878, Reel 12U)
  - Sharma, Rari Dutta, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 879, Reel 12U)
  - Sharon, Yitzhak, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 880, Reel 12U)
  - Shenstone, Allan G., 1934, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 881, Reel 12U)
  - Sheraton Corporation of America, 1958, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 882, Reel 12U)
  - Sherr, R., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 883, Reel 12U)
  - Shockley, William, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 884, Reel 12U)
  - Shockley, Mrs. William, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 885, Reel 12U)
  - Signell, Peter, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 886, Reel 12U)
  - Simmons, James E., 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 887, Reel 12U)
  - Simmons, James E., 1971, 1950-1951, 1956, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 888-889, Reel 12U)
  - Simonius, Markus, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 890, Reel 13U)
  - Singer, Albert H., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 891, Reel 13U)
  - Singh, B., 1968 (Box 22, Folder 892, Reel 13U)
  - Singh, L. S., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 893, Reel 13U)
  - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1949-1956 (Box 22, Folder 894-895, Reel 13U)
  - Slater, John C., 1951, 1967, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 896, Reel 13U)
  - Slaus, Ivo, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 897, Reel 13U)
  - Slichter, Charles P., 1972, undated (Box 22, Folder 898, Reel 13U)
  - Slobodrian, R. J., 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 899, Reel 13U)
  - Smith, Ralph L., Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 900, Reel 13U)